# Catalin Stratu



linkedin.com/in/catalin-stratu



https://github.com/CatalinStratu



catalinstratu45@gmail.com

### Summary

I started developing Crypto Job at the age of 17, at the moment Crypto Job is a platform that for 3 years has helped 100+ companies to find employees with experience in cryptocurrency. Today Crypto Job is a project that 3 people are working on

Email: catalinstratu45@gmail.com

# **Experience**



### Founder

Crypto Job

Aug 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month +)

Crypto Job - Connecting talent with opportunity.

"Crypto Job" is a leading platform to connect companies that require expertise in these areas with the best specialists thus saving time and money for companies and providing amazing opportunities for candidates.



#### Full Stack Developer

Crypto Job

Feb 2017 - Present (3 years 7 months +)

August 2020 Using MongoDB I create a monitoring System

2020 Using a Flask framework (Python) I create recommendation system for Crypto Job. and use Algolia fulltext search

2019 New RESTful API developed with Lumen

2018 I started to use GIT and Github for version control

2017 I developed Crypto Job, for the first time using: Laravel, HTML & CSS, JS

Skills & tools: PHP7, Laravel, Lumen, Eloquent ORM, RESTful API, MySQL, Mongodb, Python, Microservices, GIT



#### **PHP Developer**

Minicode

Jun 2020 - Sep 2020 (4 months)



#### Full Stack Software Engineer

**Next Cloud Link** 

Oct 2019 - Sep 2020 (1 year)

Worked on a PHP and Python apps.

Developed the MPA and Rest Api for SPA applications.

Technologies: Laravel, MongoDB, Mysql, GIT, Postgres, Rest API, ORM, Flask

#### **Education**



# Universitatea "Ştefan cel Mare" din Suceava

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

# **Honors & Awards**



# Special Prize

Dec 2019

## Skills

C++ • Data Structures • Algorithms • PHP • Start-ups • Git • Software Development • Python (Programming Language) • Go (Programming Language)